There are many ways you might want to engineer the data you've collected.
对收集的数据创建模型 可以有许多方式
Whether it's creating dummy variables or higher order terms,
无论是上节课中创建虚拟变量
as you did earlier in this lesson,
或高阶项
or one of a number of other techniques from filling in missing values,
还是填充缺失值的其他技巧之一
to scaling your data.
要测量数据
Scikit-learn and Pandas are two great libraries for feature engineering.
Scikit-learn 和 Pandas 是两个著名的特征工程库
So in the pre-processing for scikit-learn,
在 scikit-learn 预处理中
scikit-learn import pre-processing, and then you can see there's like a scale,
Scikit-learn 导入预处理 然后你会看到这样的比例
and then there's this thing called Standard scaler,
这称为 StandardScaler
there's MinMax scaler, MaxAbs Scaler,
这是 MinMax scaler MaxAbs Scaler
quantile transformer, normalization, binarization,
QuantileTransformer 归一化 二进制化
encoding categorical features, imputing missing values, custom transformations.
编码类属特征 输入缺失值 自定义转换
Let's put a few of these to practice using
我们使用一个小型数据集来练习一下
a small data set just so you can see how they work.
这样你可以明白它们如何发挥作用
So here I've created the data frame,
这里我已经创建了DataFrame
and if we take a look at this,
如果观察一下它
you can see it looks like this,
你会发现它是这样的
so I have a response X1, X2, X3,
我得到输出 X1 X2 X3
X4, X5, you can see I have some missing values,
X4 X5 你会发现有一些缺失值
I have some negative numbers,
包括一些负数
some positive numbers, this column has only ones in it.
整数 这一列中只包含 1
Notice most of these techniques have a fit transform that you
注意这些技巧的大部分包括拟合转换
can fit on your data set and then it'll transform it using the transformation described.
你可以用来拟合数据集 然后使用所描述的转换 进行转换
This is a common way of using many of the scikit-learn functions.
这是使用许多 scikit-learn 函数的一种常见方法
The reason for performing these techniques,
使用这些技巧的原因
is often to create models that are more robust,
通常是为了创建更加稳健的模型
and are not influenced by the scale of your data.
不会受到数据缩放的影响
Regression is one technique that is
回归是
impacted quite heavily by points that are far away from other points.
非常容易受到离散点严重影响的一种技巧
This can improve your predictions from the models that you make.
这样可以通过你创建的模型提高预测水平
But it does change your interpretations,
不过它确实会改变解释
similar to the way that higher order terms changed in their interpretations.
类似于高阶项改变解释的方式
Now let's try a few of these out so you can get a handle on how they work.
现在我们来练习一些 这样你可以掌握它们的原理
So Pandas has a lot of really nice features,
Pandas 具有许多很不错的特征
which you can see here in the documentation,
你可以在文档中发现这些特征
for filling in missing values.
用于填充缺失值
So, you could see by using DF mean the default was
你会发现通过使用默认值
to fill in the missing values using the mean for the columns.
使用这些列的平均值 填充缺失值
So the ones here were the mean of their remaining four ones down here,
所以这里的 1 表示下面四个 1 的平均值
and then filling in these ones with the mean of
然后填充这些 1
basically the values that weren't missing in this particular column.
利用不缺失值的这些列中值的平均数
Then, over here where we had missing values in the categorical column,
然后在我们分类列中缺失值的地方
we actually didn't get anything to fill in because taking
实际上我们无法填充什么内容
the mean of letters doesn't really make any sense.
因为得到字母的平均值没有什么意义
Let's try some of the pre-processing now so,
现在我们试一下预处理
we could do something like scale and we need to be dealing with only the X columns,
我们可以按比例缩放 只需要对 X 列进行操作
so let's use X2.
这样使用 X2
So you can see that that gave us a little bit different scaling using the min and max,
你会发现使用 min 和 max 会得到不同的缩放比例
and then the documentation can tell you exactly
这个文档告诉你
how it was calculated or why you might use it.
如何准确计算以及使用这种方法的原因
The motivation for scaling includes a robust to very small standard deviations of
按照比例缩放可以使特征的极小标准差稳健
features and for preserving the zero entries and sparse data.
保留零项和零散数据
The documentation for this stuff is really
这个文档相当不错
great and they try to give you examples of how they work here.
为你提供了这些方法原理的例子